I won't let you sign that annulment agreement
I also won't choose
your sister at the wedding
Do you want to start over for the wedding or the benefits
The years we've known each other aren't fake
You used to wait for my meetings to end
And remember my stomach issues
Gu Chengzhe, it's not me you miss
You miss how good I was to you
Because it's gone now
I can change
I'll handle the project again
I'll also draw a clear line with Su Yurou
If you want
I can apologize publicly
Mingyao, can we start over
No, Gu Chengzhe
I'm already married
Without the Fu family status
Would you still be this firm
Do you still think
I chose him because of the Fu family
Things I don't want
I won't pick back up
Su Mingyao, do you have to be this heartless